<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dimitris Alexandridis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dimitris Alexandridis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 18:44:21 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 18:44:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/education/</guid>
      <description>🚧 This page is under construction. 🚧</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 18:44:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/</guid>
      <description>Summer 2019 - Raycap, Greece – IT developer, Smart Plant Transition (Operations Dept.)  Developed online reporting pipeline (Python) of material resources consumed and parts manufactured in factory’s punching machines, effectively accelerating a primary bottleneck of the production process. Observed production stages and cooperated with technicians to identify useful performance metrics. Installed sensors and developed cloud processes (image processing, power signal analysis) that calculate the Overall Equipment Efficiency (OEE) of the factory&amp;rsquo;s manufacturing machinery (300 human operators).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/posts/2019/03/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 21:19:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019/03/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across Hugo the other day while reading this article of my dear friends at deltahacker.gr. Thought it&amp;rsquo;d be a cool little project to make a personal website using Hugo in order to get to know the glory of static website generators and tick &amp;ldquo;Make a personal website&amp;rdquo; off my weekly checklist.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a fun experience and a nice break from revising Linear Algebra.. Next task is to find out why the site&amp;rsquo;s favicon won&amp;rsquo;t appear on Chrome browsers and maybe brainstorm ways I can make use of this place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I believe that the best way to truly learn a skill, a process or an idea is to build something that demonstrates it. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to find a good reason why I am so passionate to spend so much of my free time programming and working with computers and electronic circuits. I really cannot find a definite answer to this question. I believe that my interest in computer engineering arises from my tendency to explore thought and learning: by combining computer hardware and software, an engineer can manufacture and program an intelligent machine that replicates part of their thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>